jochaho.pk 2015-04-01

# Privacy Policy

## Section 1 – What do we do with your information?

  * When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address, etc.
  * When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
  * Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

## Section 2 - Consent

### Q. How do you get my consent?

A. When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, it is implied that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for another reason, such as marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

### Q. How do I withdraw my consent?

A. If after you opt in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at support@jochaho.pk

## Section 3 - Disclosure

  * We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

## Section 4 - Third-Party Services

  * In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide.
  * However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide them for your purchase-related transactions.
  * For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
  * In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. Therefore, if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
  * Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

## Section 5 - Security

  * To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow best practices to make sure it is not lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
  * If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with an encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

## Section 6 – Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
